<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>blog on Vegan Karnataka</title>
    <link>https://vegankarnataka.in/tags/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in blog on Vegan Karnataka</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 15:51:10 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://vegankarnataka.in/tags/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Are Your Beliefs Really Your Own</title>
      <link>https://vegankarnataka.in/blogs/are-your-beliefs-really-your-own/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 15:51:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vegankarnataka.in/blogs/are-your-beliefs-really-your-own/</guid>
      <description>Over four years ago, I decided to turn vegan. Now before you feel irked by the negative connotations memes have made you associate the word &amp;ldquo;vegan&amp;rdquo; with, give me a chance to explain. I&amp;rsquo;m not writing to tell you that you should go vegan because some vegan said it&amp;rsquo;s wrong to kill animals but I&amp;rsquo;d like a chance to help you challenge yourself. Why? Because before society conditioned you into believing that animals are commodities and desensitised you from their plight, in all probability, you yourself believed that it&amp;rsquo;s wrong to kill animals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Animal Friends From the Movies</title>
      <link>https://vegankarnataka.in/blogs/our-animal-friends-from-the-movies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 14:45:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vegankarnataka.in/blogs/our-animal-friends-from-the-movies/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;re already rooting for the animals when you watch these movies.
It&amp;rsquo;s about time you started rooting for the animals in real life too!
Madagascar (2006)
Marty: Just imagine going back to nature. Back to your roots, clean air, wide open spaces! Doesn&amp;rsquo;t it bother you guys that you don&amp;rsquo;t know anything about life outside of this zoo?
Babe (1995)
Ferdinand: Look, there&amp;rsquo;s something you should know.
Babe: Yes?
Ferdinand: Humans eat ducks!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Should You Be Okay With Someones Choice to Oppress</title>
      <link>https://vegankarnataka.in/blogs/should-you-be-okay-with-someones-choice-to-oppress/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 14:42:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vegankarnataka.in/blogs/should-you-be-okay-with-someones-choice-to-oppress/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not homophobic, but it&amp;rsquo;s okay if you are.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I believe that women should have equal rights, but it&amp;rsquo;s okay if you don&amp;rsquo;t think so.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I would never kill anybody, but it&amp;rsquo;s okay if you want to.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I would never rape anybody, but it&amp;rsquo;s okay if you wish to.&amp;rdquo;
Sounds absurd right?
When you tell a vegan, &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s alright if you&amp;rsquo;re vegan, but you should also be okay with others wanting to be non-vegan&amp;rdquo;; you are quite simply saying:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Are What You Do</title>
      <link>https://vegankarnataka.in/blogs/you-are-what-you-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 14:35:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vegankarnataka.in/blogs/you-are-what-you-do/</guid>
      <description>If you believe in bodily autonomy/&amp;ldquo;my body, my choice&amp;rdquo;, grant animals the same.
If you believe in the need for agency, allow animals to have that same agency.
If you believe in rights over your own reproductive capacity, give animals the same rights.
If you are against objectification, stop participating in the objectification of animals for your pleasure.
If you know that pleasure doesn&amp;rsquo;t justify exploitation, stop using the pleasure you derive from animal products as a justification to continue exploiting animals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Our Reporting of Human Oppression Should Tell Us</title>
      <link>https://vegankarnataka.in/blogs/what-our-reporting-of-human-oppression-should-tell-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 14:06:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vegankarnataka.in/blogs/what-our-reporting-of-human-oppression-should-tell-us/</guid>
      <description>Statements I&amp;rsquo;ve heard which are meant to convey the horrific nature of oppression of humans:
It was terrible! They were treated like an animal. Leather made from human skin? Can you believe it? They treated her like a piece of meat. Studies are being conducted on rural people in developing countries as if they are lab rats. They&amp;rsquo;re literally making them the human guinea pigs. That school bus is so crowded.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
